<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <publisher>Chalmers Rekrytering</publisher>
    <publisherurl>https://chalmersrekrytering.se/lediga-jobb/</publisherurl>
    <jobs>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Work as a Frontend developer at Gung]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[Fri, 15 Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123224]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/gung-ab-johanneberg-heltid-jobba-som-frontend-utvecklare-hos-gung/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Gung AB]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <h2 id="job_description">About the company</h2> 
                <p>
                Gung AB is a growing company that works to deliver the product Gung to distributing and manufacturing companies. Gung simplifies ordering processes and complements the companies' business systems with web interfaces and APIs to increase the user experience and reduce administration. Together with 11 employees, you start from our brand new premises in Johanneberg (Gothenburg). You will be part of a very close-knit and skilled development team that has fun together.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About the service:</font> 
                <p> 
                In the role of front-end developer, you will be responsible for our deliveries to customers. You will have a team around you that will help you in this exciting and dynamic environment. We are an extremely customer-driven company and in the role you are required to have qualities that are always aimed at delivering customer value. Together with our other developers, project managers and sales people, you will be the driving force in establishing processes that ensure our deliveries to customers.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About you:</font> 
                <p>
                We want you to have at least three years of experience from JS client frameworks (Preferably Angular but it is not a requirement), it can mean everything from experience in the workplace to hobby programming in your spare time. You are passionate about development and problem solving and can help others achieve the same goals as yourself. Techniques that you are used to using are Angular, Bootstrap, HTML, databases such as MongoDB & SQL server and version control in GIT. We employ you because we believe that you can develop into a long-term part of our team that wants to take our company, our product, our customers to the next level and of course be a contributor to creating a wonderful workplace. For the right person, we offer a good salary, benefits, opportunity for profit sharing, inspiring conferences and more.
                The position refers to a full-time position, but the opportunity to work part-time is also considered. We work continuously with the recruitment process and therefore recommend that you submit your application as soon as possible.  
                If you have any thoughts, questions or want to know more about the role, it is great to contact Martin Hörnell at Chalmers Student Union Recruitment.
                martin.hornell@chalmersrekrytering.se
                </p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[Sunday, 14th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Are you looking for a flexible extra job during your engineering studies? Look here!]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[6 Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123234]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/sveriges-ingenjorer-goteborg-deltid-soker-du-ett-flexibelt-extrajobb-under-dina-ingenjorsstudier-se-hit/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Sveriges Ingenjörer]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <p>
                Are you looking for a flexible extra job during your engineering studies? Look here! Now Tarik is looking for new colleagues at Chalmers. Here he talks about his experience as a Student Marketer at Sveriges Ingenjörer:
                </p>
                <h2 id="job_description">What can you do as a Student Marketer?</h2> 
                <p>
                As a student marketer, you can do everything from standing at the event, handing out coffee to helping or giving lectures. What all activities have in common is that you get to meet a lot of people who you try to recruit or help with their membership.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">What is the best thing about the mission?</font> 
                <p> 
                The best thing is that it is very social, which makes the work shifts fun. You meet a lot of people you talk to so time just flies by when you work.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">What has the assignment given you?</font> 
                <p>
                The most rewarding thing must have been that I have become more confident and less nervous when I talk to strangers. Because you meet so many people, you also get to learn to talk to different types of people.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Why should engineering students apply for this particular assignment?</font> 
                <p>
                It is important to have social skills in working life, which you develop when you work as a student marketer. In addition, you learn a lot about union issues that can benefit you when, for example, you have to negotiate your salary in the future.
                How to apply? Go to @sverigesingenjorer on Instagram and click on the link in the cinema to apply.
                </p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[parttime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[6th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

       
    </jobs>
</source>
