<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <publisher>Chalmers Rekrytering</publisher>
    <publisherurl>https://chalmersrekrytering.se/lediga-jobb/</publisherurl>
    <jobs>
        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Programmer at See/refine]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[Fri, 24 Sept 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123123]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/en/job/see-refine-gothenburg-heltid-programmer-at-see-refine/;source=Indeed]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[See/refine]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <imageUrl>https://chalmersrekrytering.se/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Seerefine3555-350x350.jpg</imageUrl>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <h2 id="job_description">About the Company:</h2> 
                <p>See/refine is a small and exciting international company with its office situated in Gothenburg. The company has just left the start-up phase and is growing rapidly.

                See/refine provide expertise in digital business transformation using a toolbox of IOT, machine learning in combination with modern web technologies. See/refine, among other things, builds mobile fleet management services for large service companies. Their platforms enables more than 100 people to work together in a simple and efficient way.

                What is important for See/refine is your personal development and you will get a lot of responsibility early so you can grow your knowledge and skills. </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About the job:</font> 
                <p> The job is a full-time position as programmer at See/refine. As a member of the See/refine team you will work with development of hybrid apps and web applications which are based on the latest web technology. You will interact with hardware and manage large amount of data.

                Your work will range from understanding the customer’s requirements to development, test and release. Most of your work will be consultancy based and as an employee you will have a great chance to form and affect your own role and the company’s future. The company values work-life balance and has a two-week getaway to a foreign location every year. </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About you:</font> 
                <p> 
                We are looking for you who has an interest in programming and want to excel in your role. We believe that you already have some knowledge in programming but want to take your skills to the next level. As an individual you are ambitious, curious and likes to take responsibility. As your tasks will be consultancy based, we see you as communicative and solution oriented forming fantastic new services with See/refine’s customers.

                If you have any questions regarding the opening at Seerefine, please contact Alexandra Alto, alexandra.alto@chalmersrekrytering.se
                </p> 
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[Sun, 31st October 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Work as a Frontend developer at Gung]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[Fri, 15 Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123224]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/gung-ab-johanneberg-heltid-jobba-som-frontend-utvecklare-hos-gung/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Gung AB]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <h2 id="job_description">About the company</h2> 
                <p>
                Gung AB is a growing company that works to deliver the product Gung to distributing and manufacturing companies. Gung simplifies ordering processes and complements the companies' business systems with web interfaces and APIs to increase the user experience and reduce administration. Together with 11 employees, you start from our brand new premises in Johanneberg (Gothenburg). You will be part of a very close-knit and skilled development team that has fun together.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About the service:</font> 
                <p> 
                In the role of front-end developer, you will be responsible for our deliveries to customers. You will have a team around you that will help you in this exciting and dynamic environment. We are an extremely customer-driven company and in the role you are required to have qualities that are always aimed at delivering customer value. Together with our other developers, project managers and sales people, you will be the driving force in establishing processes that ensure our deliveries to customers.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About you:</font> 
                <p>
                We want you to have at least three years of experience from JS client frameworks (Preferably Angular but it is not a requirement), it can mean everything from experience in the workplace to hobby programming in your spare time. You are passionate about development and problem solving and can help others achieve the same goals as yourself. Techniques that you are used to using are Angular, Bootstrap, HTML, databases such as MongoDB & SQL server and version control in GIT. We employ you because we believe that you can develop into a long-term part of our team that wants to take our company, our product, our customers to the next level and of course be a contributor to creating a wonderful workplace. For the right person, we offer a good salary, benefits, opportunity for profit sharing, inspiring conferences and more.
                The position refers to a full-time position, but the opportunity to work part-time is also considered. We work continuously with the recruitment process and therefore recommend that you submit your application as soon as possible.  
                If you have any thoughts, questions or want to know more about the role, it is great to contact Martin Hörnell at Chalmers Student Union Recruitment.
                martin.hornell@chalmersrekrytering.se
                </p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[Sunday, 14th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Junior consultants to Stockholm for start in August 2022]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[Sunday, 10 Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123245]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/deloitte-stockholm-heltid-juniora-konsulter-till-stockholm-for-start-i-augusti-2022/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Deloitte]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <p>
                Deloitte offers services in auditing, business consulting, financial advice, risk management, tax advice and related areas. With more than 345,000 employees in over 150 countries, we help our clients and the world around us to solve complex problems and achieve high goals. What defines Deloitte is our quest to make a meaningful difference. We believe that as our clients and our community grow stronger, so will we! It is therefore obvious for us to run initiatives such as WorldClass, WorldClimate and our strategy for diversity, ALL IN.
                <font style="font-weight:bold">
                Do you want to work with strategic change projects or the introduction of digital transformation projects? Continue to develop into a successful team of 300 people in Sweden, with over 345,000 colleagues around the world? We are looking for junior consultants for our service area Consulting in Stockholm, starting in August 2022.
                </font> 
                </p>
                <h2 id="job_description">About the role</h2> 
                <p>
                At Deloitte's Consulting department, you work to support leading organizations in their toughest challenges. Our services range from analysis of strategic issues, to the implementation of complex change projects at the core of the client's business. To meet the changing demands of the market, we support our clients' journeys of change with new ways of working, efficient processes, optimized organization and help them implement system solutions based on modern digital platforms.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Deloitte Consulting is organized into the following five areas to meet our clients' needs:</font> 
                <p> 
                Core Business Operations supports our clients in implementing business strategies to achieve their business goals. We work with business change, which often includes the implementation of system support for industry-specific technology in several different industries, with a special focus on banking and insurance and the public sector. 

                Customer & Marketing supports our clients in their marketing, commerce, sales and service processes to build value-creating customer relationships. We do this by helping our clients develop their customer meeting, their organization and system support for these functions. Our work ranges from strategy and consulting, to agile IT deliveries where we deliver leading platforms from Adobe, Salesforce and SAP.

                Enterprise Technology & Performance supports our clients to get the most out of their investments in the areas of Finance, Supply Chain and IT operations by acting as support from strategy development to design of business processes and implementation of business systems, often based on SAP. 

                Human Capital supports our clients to run and develop their business through their most important asset: the employees. We ensure that transformations have a sustainable effect on the organization, guide our clients in developing and creating the HR of the future and the work of the future, and select and implement cloud system support that is equipped to meet the challenges and expectations of the future.

                Strategy, Analytics and M&A support our clients in their strategic issues concerning, for example, business strategies, marketing and sales strategies, innovation and business development, acquisition strategies and more comprehensive strategic transformation initiatives. We combine deep expertise in strategy, M&A, innovation, digitization and analytics to provide tailored advice that drives value for our clients. 
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">We are looking for:</font> 
                <p>
                We are looking for you who are a newly graduated civil engineer, systems scientist, economist with a master's / master's degree or who have an equivalent degree. You also have:
                <ul>
                    <li>Good study results, international experience and relevant commitment alongside the studies.</li>
                    <li>A great interest in how digitalisation and new technology can develop businesses and contribute to the realization of our clients' strategies and business goals. </li>
                    <li>Very good language skills in Swedish and English in both speech and writing.</li>
                    <li>Above all, you are a team player, have a good ability to prioritize, are analytical and have a burning interest in developing business and operations.</li>
                    <li>You are keen to work with different teams, mix skills and learn from each other, to solve our clients' challenges together. </li>
                    <li>Since our clients are both within and outside Sweden, travel and work in another place can be included in your work.</li>
                </ul>
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">We Offer:</font> 
                <p>
                Access to a global network of experienced colleagues that you can use to develop both yourself, our clients and our business. You get great opportunities for international projects and exchanges, both on a global and Nordic level. You get to work with exciting, complex assignments in teams that always value your perspective. Through practical experience, a coach who supports your career, education and continuous feedback, you get help to take advantage of your strengths.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Application:</font> 
                <p>
                You apply online. Your application must consist of a CV, personal letter, and transcripts from college / university and high school. Note that you need to upload all documents for your application to be considered complete. Submit your application no later than 24/10. Selection will take place after the last application day.

                As a qualitative part of Deloitte's recruitment process, our final candidates undergo a background check, in order to increase awareness of our future employees, secure the working environment for our employees and meet regulatory requirements. The process for background checks is carried out in collaboration with ToFindOut. 
                <url>https://tofindout.se/sv/faq/ </url>
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Questions:</font>
                <p>
                Welcome to contact Sophie Karlerö, recruiter at Deloitte, on telephone 070-080 27 77. 
 
                We look forward to your application!
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">What impact will you make?</font>
                <p>
                At Deloitte, your work makes a meaningful difference, every day, as you grow into an inclusive corporate culture of collaboration and high performance. In addition to creating solutions, we strive to make a positive and decisive difference for others in our environment, our clients and society. At Deloitte, you will find previously hidden opportunities to succeed and realize your full potential.
                </p>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[Tue, 9th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Are you looking for a flexible extra job during your engineering studies? Look here!]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[6 Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123234]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/sveriges-ingenjorer-goteborg-deltid-soker-du-ett-flexibelt-extrajobb-under-dina-ingenjorsstudier-se-hit/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Sveriges Ingenjörer]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <p>
                Are you looking for a flexible extra job during your engineering studies? Look here! Now Tarik is looking for new colleagues at Chalmers. Here he talks about his experience as a Student Marketer at Sveriges Ingenjörer:
                </p>
                <h2 id="job_description">What can you do as a Student Marketer?</h2> 
                <p>
                As a student marketer, you can do everything from standing at the event, handing out coffee to helping or giving lectures. What all activities have in common is that you get to meet a lot of people who you try to recruit or help with their membership.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">What is the best thing about the mission?</font> 
                <p> 
                The best thing is that it is very social, which makes the work shifts fun. You meet a lot of people you talk to so time just flies by when you work.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">What has the assignment given you?</font> 
                <p>
                The most rewarding thing must have been that I have become more confident and less nervous when I talk to strangers. Because you meet so many people, you also get to learn to talk to different types of people.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Why should engineering students apply for this particular assignment?</font> 
                <p>
                It is important to have social skills in working life, which you develop when you work as a student marketer. In addition, you learn a lot about union issues that can benefit you when, for example, you have to negotiate your salary in the future.
                How to apply? Go to @sverigesingenjorer on Instagram and click on the link in the cinema to apply.
                </p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[parttime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[6th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Do you have an interest in finance? Are you driven by fun and free work and are looking for the next big challenge?]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[5 Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique223234]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/wenden-rydholm-goteborg-deltid-heltid-internship-har-du-ett-intresse-for-ekonomi-drivs-du-av-ett-roligt-samt-fritt-arbete-och-pa-jakt-efter-nasta-stora-utmaning/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Wendén & Rydholm]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <h2 id="job_description">Role:</h2>
                <p>
                Accounting consultant and financial management.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About you:</font> 
                <p>
                You want to work with us at Wendén & Rydholm because we all share the vision of entrepreneurship. Our finance agency is a place where we are challenged and developed rather than somewhere you just go to "work". Driven and will is the most important thing, you learn the tools and methods. We are looking for you who are social and enjoy working in a small company where you can grow with us. You are service-minded towards customers and do not hesitate to do business when the opportunity arises.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Tasks:</font> 
                <p>
                As a newcomer to Wendén & Rydholm, you are given the chance to work with accounting and financial management, where you are given an understanding of how business economics works from the ground up. An ordinary week you work with financial accounting, customer contact, financial advice and tax planning for companies & owners. You work in a close-knit team and report directly to partners at the company.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Merit:</font> 
                <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Experience of accounting, accounting and board work.</li>
                    <li>Good knowledge of excel. </li>
                    <li>Experience of sales or some form of customer contact.</li>
                </ul>
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">We offer:</font> 
                <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>To become part of a driven entrepreneurial group and to carry out a job as a self-employed person..</li>
                    <li>To expand your understanding in accounting and financial management.</li>
                    <li>A very generous commission model that provides good opportunities for co-ownership in future joint projects.</li>
                    <li>Great freedom under responsibility where you plan your own working hours.</li>
                    <li>To work with your own personal customer portfolio.</li>
                </ul>
                The position refers to a full-time position, but the opportunity to work part-time or practice is also considered. We work continuously with the recruitment process and therefore recommend that you submit your application as soon as possible. If you have any thoughts, questions or want to know more about the role, it is great to contact the responsible recruiter

                 <a href = "mailto:magdalena.lopes@chalmersrekrytering.se">Magdalena Lopes</a>
                </p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[Internship, fulltime, parttime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[6th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

       <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Students studying M, Z, D, IT, or E for project within autonomous systems – 140 SEK/h]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[4th Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique323234]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/chalmers-tekniska-hogskola-chalmers-goteborg-deltid-third-year-students-studying-m-z-d-it-or-e-for-project-within-autonomous-systems-140-sek-h/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Chalmers Tekniska Högskola]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Chalmers, Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <font style="font-weight:bold">
                We are looking for engineering students for the project:
                Towards unified international teaching and learning of
                autonomous systems: The Kiwi 2.0 platform
                </font> 
                <h2 id="job_description">Overview:</h2> 
                <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Looking for third year students studying M, Z, D, IT, or E (or with corresponding skills).</li>
                    <li>Several students will work in parallel, optionally in teams.</li>
                    <li>Payed 140 SEK per worked hour, from a given time budget (based on results).</li>
                    <li>Excellent for the CV: “Design and development of a teaching platform for autonomous systems”.</li>
                    <li>An excellent way of helping future generations of students, and to spread Chalmers great tech and teaching internationally.</li>
                    <li>Tasks within CAD, PCB design, vehicle design, teaching material design, and web platform design.</li>
                    <li>Just send an email for more information and an individual offer!</li>
                </ul>
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Task and goal summary:</font> 
                <p>
                In 2016, Chalmers initiated the work on a accessible opensource and open-hardware platform to teach autonomous systems to students. The platform ended up as a largely 3Dprintable platform that could be proceeded in large volumes. So far, it was used in many popular courses at Chalmers and as a tool to teach autonomous systems to PhD students within the WASP programme. The Kiwi platform is also the main educational tool towards the OpenDLV framework. Currently, there are about 45 Kiwi cars already built at Chalmers. During spring 2021, a master thesis has investigated how the platform can be used as a tool for learning autonomous systems and software also outside academia, on high-schools and in hobbyist communities. The outcome of the work was encouraging, but it also highlighted several ways to further improve the platform to make it even more accessible! The current goal we are working towards is an online community connected to the Kiwi car and the learning of OpenDLV, in English and Spanish, targeting the general public in Europe, USA, and South America. However, in parallel with the wide introduction we would like to find a refinement of the hardware platform to increase our chances on other markets.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">ask and goal summary:</font>
                <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Based on the current Kiwi design, make a new design that: (1) is less expensive, (2) more durable, (3) easier to 3D-print, (4) uses more accessible electronics, (5) provides better maneuverability, and (6) addresses some known technical shortcomings.</li>
                    <li>Try to keep some level of backwards compatibility so that the old cars can be retrofitted.</li>
                    <li>Update the manufacturing and assembly instructions online.</li>
                    <li>Update the online coding tutorials to target Kiwi 2.0.</li>
                </ul>
                If you have interest in the position please send in your application and we get back too you.
                </p>
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[parttime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[4th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Junior Management Consultant - Recruitment Day]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[4th Oct 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique423234]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/effso-stockholm-goteborg-heltid-junior-managementkonsult-rekryteringsdag/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[EFFSO]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Stockholm, Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <font style="font-weight:bold">
                Are you attracted to the consulting life where strategy work and transformation projects are your everyday life but at the same time want to be involved in the implementation of changes? Or have you considered a line role in the industry but want greater variety in the tasks and influence in the development of organizations? Then we can be the right company for you!
                </font> 
                <h2 id="job_description">About EFFSO's consulting business:</h2> 
                <p>
                EFFSO is a purchasing consulting company. We help companies, large and small, to develop their purchasing business. With us, you can be involved in implementing everything from individual category projects at a customer to coordinating major transformations of a company's purchasing function with several hundred employees.

                We value commitment and a willingness to pursue change work. We believe that you have analytical ability with both an eye for detail and an understanding of the whole. If you are also a humble person with a great desire to both teach and teach, we have come to the right place.

                Our customers are in all industries and in both the private and public sectors.

                We are a consulting company that is characterized by a pragmatic approach to most things and a kind culture. With us, work-life balance is more than just words and "the team in front of the self" is more important than individual achievements. Read more about us at effso.se.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">We Offer:</font> 
                <p>
                We believe that development is important and we therefore attach great importance to training our consultants. When you start at EFFSO, you will undergo an introductory program that prepares you for the consulting role in various ways. For the first one to two years, you will work with more senior consultants, receive regular feedback and a lot of help to develop your ability for structure, problem solving, strategy and communication. We work with a high degree of freedom under responsibility and support each other in our quest to constantly improve on helping our customers create outstanding results. At EFFSO, you will constantly learn new things, develop and be challenged.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About the Role:</font>
                <p>
                As a junior management consultant at EFFSO, you get the opportunity to work with exciting purchasing issues and change management in several different companies and industries. The role requires a good ability to get acquainted with different businesses, understand our customers' needs and quickly start delivering results. You will be an important part of different teams on a project basis. The work is run on a fact-based basis with processes and methodology as support. This means that you will quickly have to take great responsibility and that you will have a clear development in your consulting role at an early stage.
                Tasks will vary but include:
                <ul>
                    <li>Carry out qualitative and quantitative analyzes, e.g. total cost analyzes and market analyzes</li>
                    <li>Manage stakeholders within customer teams and customer organizations</li>
                    <li>Implementation of improvement activities at our customers</li>
                    <li>Ensure results and improvement for our customers by supporting them throughout the projects</li>
                    <li>Build your own customer relationships with the customer organizations through the projects</li>
                    <li>Be an important part of developing EFFSO as a company</li>
                </ul>
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Your profile:</font> 
                <p>
                We are looking for you who are passionate about developing and doing things better. You have the ability to identify potential for improvement and you love to drive change. We believe that you look forward to starting work in a consulting role in teams. We hope that you have a desire to learn the consulting work where the focus will be on details, structure and progress. You are probably currently in the final stages of your academic education or you have taken your degree in the last year (preferably a master's degree in engineering or similar). To succeed, you need to be persistent, analytical, solution-oriented, structured and humble. If you are also interested in the shopping area, that is a big plus.

                As a person, you are curious, open and the one who is motivated by new challenges. We believe that you are very communicative and responsive and that you are open to other people's solutions - for you it is more important that it is right than that you are right.
                </p>

                <font style="font-weight:bold">Location:</font> 
                <p>
                We are looking for employees both to Stockholm and to Gothenburg.
                The service often includes a varying degree of travel as our customers are in several locations.
                </p>

                <font style="font-weight:bold">Application</font> 
                <p>
                Do you want to be part of a wonderful group of consultants who are all passionate about developing purchasing organizations? Then send your application (CV, grade extract and a personal letter) to us no later than October 8, 2021 for the chance to participate in our recruitment day on November 16.

                For questions regarding recruitment, you are welcome to contact Kristina Tengroth at kristina.tengroth (at) effso.se.
                </p>

                <font style="font-weight:bold">About EFFSO</font> 
                <p>
                With us, we who share EFFSO's values thrive. We choose to believe in the good in people and we are convinced that joy in work contributes to exceptional results. Our goal is to create a strong commitment from everyone we meet and to develop our employees, customers and EFFSO. 

                We strive for long-term relationships and trusting collaborations. As an employee at EFFSO, you will be part of our network with purchasing profiles from all industries and levels. We offer continuous competence development, are happy to share our knowledge and give you the opportunity to grow in your professional role. EFFSO takes into account the different conditions of people and sees different experiences as an asset.
                </p>

                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[4th November 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job> 

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Audit Internship at KPMG]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[16th Sept 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique523234]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/job/kpmg-audit-internship-i-stockholm-goteborg-stockholm-internship-audit-internship-at-kpmg/]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[KPMG - Audit Internship i Stockholm]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Stockholm, Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <font style="font-weight:bold">
                Are you curious about a career in auditing? KPMG now offers students the opportunity to test on the job as an accountant during the financial statements, which gives you as a student a unique opportunity to gain an understanding of what the role as an accountant entails and the challenges that KPMG's customers face.
                </font> 

                <h2 id="job_description">Your role as an internal audit at KPMG:</h2> 
                <p>
                As a student, you have the chance to try out the job as an assistant accountant for eight weeks between January and February at our head office in Stockholm. As an internal audit, you will work during our high season, when it happens most in the industry, and thus gain insight into how both we at KPMG and our customers work. You will work on several different client assignments together with our auditing teams and the tasks consist of tasks that graduate newly hired auditing assistants usually perform. This is a fantastic opportunity for you who want to supplement theory with practice and test if you thrive in the environment at one of the Big4 agencies, while you gain valuable experience for your upcoming career. This is a paid internship and you work full time (40 hi a week).
                </p>

                <font style="font-weight:bold">Your qualities and qualifications:</font> 
                <p>
                We are looking for you who are in the final stages of your studies and have the opportunity to work full time during the first block of the spring semester. The working period runs from January to February. Of course, there is flexibility regarding absence for exams or the like.

                You have the will, commitment and ambition to develop into an accountant who works to make a difference and improve the future of our customers and the world around us. You are team-oriented, outgoing, have a good analytical ability and are happy to take your own initiatives. If you have previous professional experience in finance, service or sales, this is an advantage. Furthermore, it is a plus if you have engaged outside of your studies. We also see that you have good knowledge of Swedish and English and a great interest in auditing.

                Do you want to make a difference with us?
                If you think you are the right person for the role and want to take on a new challenge, we look forward to your application containing CV, personal letter, transcripts from university / college, references with contact information and high school grades. We will interview interesting candidates on an ongoing basis, so do not wait with your application.

                Choosing a future employer and career is an important choice. If you have questions regarding KPMG as a workplace or about our recruitment process, you are welcome to contact Jonatan Lundberg, <a href = "mailto: jonatan.lundberg@kpmg.se">Send Email</a>. KPMG does not have the opportunity to cover any travel costs or housing costs in Stockholm, but the application is open to students from all over the country.

                We look forward to receiving your application!
                </p>

                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[parttime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[16th Oct 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job> 


    </jobs>
</source>
